what up I'm just telling scoping for
giraffe yo so re from slack cent come AI
a beautiful Ford giraffe
not that that's a wire Ford giraffe
alright so let's go get some cable ties
out of this box here yeah yeah re
all right let's go out and I got the
Ford key in my pocket
let's go to the Ford I hope no one took
before someone took the Ford a few
nights ago I woke up was like three in
the morning I wanna go to McDonald's
true story
oh we got a lot of cars alright I
probably just lock myself out of the
house but I got my Ford key here am i
right year of the four
you're the floor da so here we are
climbing aboard my beautiful Ford Fusion
I love this car
now we don't a smartlock I'll trust that
shit man hackers you all watch out for
hackers man what about hackers alright
so I don't know if you really see
anything phones not very good in the
dark Oh in here oh it's up here cool so
just go right in here I'm gonna
disconnect this connect it well first we
can just connect whoa we lost all the
lights here let's get some lights on in
here
yes p8 2 6 6 the hackers bro what about
hackers though have you considered
hackers yeah I know I know I know I've
come around on the fusion guys you know
I changed my mind when I'm wrong I was
wrong about bubble I um I know it's
wrong about Ford I was not wrong about
zooks and I was not wrong about Drive
that I got but maybe I'll come around on
them too you know I can change my mind
that's I'm not a politician no no see
that's just too far man Subaru is too
far all right yeah yeah things change
yeah shot back home today alright let's
go V sorry I need to hold you like this
I cool so
eyeliner you know I've never been aunt
eyeliner um so we got these connectors
here so let's plug this dongle into this
dongle don't save dongle it triggers
area Richards or whatever name was all
right let's plug in this dongle
sorry it's cookies I know I know I'm
being rough is it fed I don't know if
it's just my for giraffe outfit am I
gonna have to contact oh well I'm gonna
put you guys right there well I try to
do this with two hands oh that's gonna
go in like that I say ah plugging it in
backwards I got ya alright so let's go
here alright look at that for giraffe
installs look at that cool okay so we
don't need this wire down here anymore
unplug my grape and uh come down here
there's my great panda down there you
know we got the latest stuff from shop
comm about AI because we are comment on
the I and you can go to shop like come
over there and you can buy this kind of
stuff too and therefore draft aspect so
let's see plug this guy here we go bro
this is fourth year right now
I know it's your the Ford that's right
and thank you are we can even make this
for giraffe so all the Scoobies are
about to find out live whether you're
for giraffe works or not let's first see
if we have power oh yeah we got power
all right all right cool cool little
smooth jazz we can we can definitely
lose the smooth jazz yeah yeah that's
better
yeah right we got a rap hang on I gotta
put your sax coppice she don't want to
be saved
yeah Jay Coleman shit bang alright so we
got my grape and a wire right here
and we got my wire that can with my Aeon
no I'm over Sony you guys I don't think
about so many much anymore all right so
you all check out my flippin Dion
this is a normally hunt not not a weird
prototype you have a prototype the ads
are canceled they kind of sucked not
secret oh it already detected started
Wow
I don't know about this is crazy so I'm
just undoing this wire we can so you
guys see that I got a already flip Durio
nice where's my comma shirt and I went a
code did shut all right so we got we got
my grape and a thing up here
I'm always looking crazy guys I'm gonna
shave the beard oh yeah I'm shaving the
beard tomorrow this show only if the
release happens it's gonna cable tie
this up
all right I think we are ready to Ford
these cable ties am i oh no Lane keep
assist malfunction
no no that's not good all right that's
it that's it what's up I think we're
good let's go I'm gonna pull my seat up
let's go for a little Drive we'll go to
cabana and see we see
thanks for driving a hybrid you're
welcome for it it's missing a little
piece you might have to promise losses
Kofi's I I think we're good I don't see
errors now ready to drive let's go bros
we're gonna need some lights
where'd you get this by the way
I love tennis so if you own all of to us
what does this my girl shouldn't know
who I am
but if I ever did I would date Taylor
Swift a letter a song about me all right
you know what guys no I don't even know
if we have to drive I have a new idea I
think if I go into the settings here I
can actually get it to vibrate the lane
no not that that's entertainment
he's all we gotta use this one all right
oh there we go help no ah there we go
great you have to press the left arrow
go to KFC we ain't gonna care zebras
we're driving right now so pay attention
to the road we don't have open power but
you do have all pot you still have to
pay attention right what's in the
settings menu no we're gonna try the
settings menu once we get home driver
assist lane keep system intensity if you
change the intensity I see look it
vibrates the wheel intensity high so
we'll just remember that I did this
mirror up that we like all let's go
so let's remember I do that that light
I'm gonna check it out with your battery
oh this guy wants to race I'm not racing
some guy at a red car man I got a white
hybrid here let's go to cabana cool cool
boss alright so now I gotta wait for my
Aeon to upload should already be coming
mmm good city I don't know about that I
can't leave my lights on there by my
Ford let's go to cabana
[Music]
hmm let's see let me close what's up on
my computer
no I don't like showing you guys the top
of my computer oh no no that's closed
get me for a little bit while I find
that route yeah we got a grape and of
course but then again let's see what's
up
oh yeah my burgers coming soon that's
exciting
Oh see you change your desk again no the
same desk all right let me just connect
to the fusion here I hope routes are
processing yes how's the processing oh
they upload it so fast oh you guys won't
wait what no that's yesterday's that's
literally no bad thingy
it hasn't processed your upload is
running nope we might be out of luck we
might just be out of block any noises a
giraffe make that's a good question no
my route hasn't uploaded yet I don't
understand
yeah rap battle brah
your bun 2 equals spy doesn't spy just
said connected to the Wi-Fi so we have
an internal interface here where I can
manage all of our company eons put me on
inside all this so much effort I have to
go get the Aeon honestly it seems like
Wi-Fi is broken no that's yesterday's
Drive you guys you guys guess who's
starting on Monday we have an
infrastructure engineer starting at
Monday that's gonna fix that problem
no you bumped it's fun I mean I
installed X Mona Dan got shit um no this
is terrible I'm gonna go wait okay hang
on now I'm connected to the Aeon it
moved though when connected over
cellular to be you know capable Wi-Fi
okay so I'm connected to the cameras and
shit I understand why the route didn't
process though Andy Andy among periscope
my route didn't process I'm on periscope
I don't see my routes like a nice like
your dog's ID yeah ah dear time to STP I
froze we gonna see fate you wanna ask
you if you have video of me will see
your food we can use a front camera I'm
saying about ID there should be this
route yeah I know we hired it if you're
such a guy he starts Monday so now we'll
have somebody to I'll blame if things
take forever
I'll go through the checklist here's the
checklist for zero for floor guys go to
the checklist I gotta make the front
camera work at night never give up never
surrender absolutely that's the motto
you guys 64 you were watching you guys
don't know shop comedy I make sure to
buy we got the dopest merch in the game
you can buy Aeons like this one here you
can buy deep up boards pandas pause ah
yeah a rough Monday coming up I know yo
guess what else
you know we hired today we hired over
prudent we hired a recruiter we have
heard a lot of people we hired a lot of
people lately you know we've been hiring
cuz we got money but we're not talking
about that what any plans to keep my
cars on the rails like crews I don't
know what that means but let's let's
download a picture of my face and see if
we're gonna watch a video of me that's
SCPA I guess CPR phone so calming I bug
bounty now if you find bugs go hack
people we don't care just kidding
there's no bounty just report them cuz
you're nice or you can like I don't know
how is the HD mapping coming no you want
to go visit the HD mapping team getting
a visibility team can go into that menu
right here here's a recording for the
front camera it's not very good at night
you see that giraffe toggling there you
can kind of see my face over there okay
I'm holding the skull piece
while we wait patiently for my route to
process all right band up no but you
want to go visit you want to go visit
upstairs team and talk about why we
don't have maps yet let's go visit off
Jays team and you know you always play
McCallum filter problem to the scope
ease yeah
[Music]
I understand it just explains come on
okay so we're trying to write a new
Kalman filter architecture that
represents attitude in a new way so you
can represent your attitude in the world
using Euler angles which is three
different angles and that's just those
three angles represent how you rotate
your reference frame to get into the car
frame yeah um but that's singular and
like nonlinear because when you go over
to PI it comes back so there's like to
trillions which is a better way of
representing it but that's a
four-dimensional vector whereas guys how
many dimensions is rotation how many
dimensions to get where does the other
dimension go it goes over here yeah you
need to get one of those matrices that
big like the big fight big be this big
we need big five matrix but you can't
get the big financials because it's not
a Jacobian these F matrix is Jacobian
and that's good
big five matrix is not Jacobian guys I
really tried hard last night typing
Jacobian to get it we tried like a bunch
of different combinations of Jacobian
you only do that so so now just just so
you guys know just who use copies when
you ask about the HD maps okay you
dropped out of math in high school but
that's why Khan Academy exists it's
absolutely bro
yeah so just you guys know that's where
the HD gaps are who want to change the
world come work at come AI let's see my
rap process yeah do the process no it
didn't
this is a tragedy engineer Johnny Monday
and then like you know give him some
time give a few months like you want to
do slam right because even with a gray
panda if you want to get that crazy high
accuracy you know you got to allegedly
ya know the even uploaded that's not the
problem it just seems like the pipeline
didn't process them yeah guys it's gonna
get better
this year we're gonna you know get a lot
of people this you I don't a lot of
people yeah give an update on Monday
we're gonna increase the yeah yeah I was
gonna I was gonna Cabana like them we
got a Ford giraffe in the now so we're
gonna take a look at yeah um less
measures of the giraffe with obd
interesting which phone are we using
after the oh oh no only the one plus
three teeth that's it ever this is the
jet right like look we got like
debugging right here at coming on well
let's check Twitter that's what I do and
I have nothing to do it's kind of
terrible yeah we're running all this on
Anton if by Anton you mean a flown yet
bra
no no no phones are phones are
incredible man
phones are quad-core yo guys free the
DSP comm check it out right now it's
just a tweet but they'll be way more no
yeah we use a Windows server we use ms
sq what do you think
dance team of freedom shoes don't tell
anyone yet the DSP got freedom no but we
got lead DSP exploits you know used to
be hacker in a past life yeah it is this
well you know waiting for the right time
to announce the freedom the DSP um just
use AWS servers but not in either yes
we're using Azure why can't you make
mine from the maps because we're a
hardware company we make money from a
hardware and then we give the maps away
for free um no wait the Qualcomm DSP
wanna call come DSP yeah you guys you're
uploading so many drives that we can't
keep up no but seriously guys growth has
been you want to talk about moon it's
been moon around here this store yeah
how we fulfilled twice a week we might
have just start fulfilling more and not
because we want to ship quicker but
because that's just how crazy things are
flying off the shelves
we've moved like move like hundreds of
eons thousands of pandas you know okay
we're getting to that we're getting to
that thousand and ten thousand mark tip
which is which is getting crazy oh you
guys saw the pandas right
zombie Netta phones you're right bill
the pen off the compounds crazy thing so
I don't know if this route is gonna come
through and process oh oh yo okay well
at least I can see my files now so those
miles this is our internal tool that's
my dog lady there's no secrets on there
um get around guns yeah we are kind of
you know get ariane early we've probably
made to few yawns okay so when we first
sold yawns like nobody even understood
what it was and nobody like bought any
and now we sell like lots and lots of
eons and yeah so we're looking into
someone's got to call me back about some
big purchases so we can make a lot more
eons right all right so let's watch the
camera watch the video of my drive okay
here's here's the video that
high-quality hd are all blurry but I
don't think it's blank this is blur cuz
I didn't clean my windshield yeah dirt
LayCool s1 yo do you know where I can
buy ten thousand of them if you could
hook me up you know where I could get a
lot of Legos oh yeah you know you don't
want a neo bro yeah but you're gonna
want it you're gonna want to switch the
problem with switching is you want to
get that uh I know right if you know how
to hook me up with a lot of Legos got a
lot that's the laughs I Drive a lot
let's see my round finished processing
we're gonna give you guys more access to
this tool to this is we call it user
admin no they haven't processed yet oh
man you know crispy these pictures look
Oh actually I don't think the focus
really had time look at yourself crispy
that picture locks
that's a crispy looking picture
called user admin you know doesn't
remind you of anything like that that
sounds like someone they don't want to
come here and intern and write that
what about why Dart
I bought a lidar a long time ago I
regret it I don't need a lidar shoe
expensive man we have money like now we
have money again but you know we're
frugal very frugal
it's got to be frugal we pay people well
there's always votes no money oh come
right that I hire from New Zealand no
you gotta get a working California
see really guys just on the DL if you
know where to get like a couple thousand
Legos or one pluses let me know we're
gonna be Eddie and I are gonna be taking
a trip to China soon I don't know bank
account is actually not going dry we're
almost profitable now we're like we
would be profitable if we just hire all
these new people but we hired all these
new people she don't regret it all cuz
they're great people I am so it's like
not processing yeah you guys are
uploading too many yeah oh I will
definitely periscope from the People's
Republic of China absolutely Auto
high-beam I'm alright in that shit what
are your tips are raising money if
you're asking me that you you change
your idea or like change your pitch like
you just let me tell you the how to
raise money just act like you don't want
it because if you want it smells like
desperation build a good product right
we didn't need the money like you know
but we got on great terms so you know
you notice said no to great terms um no
the money's gonna help us grow I mean
the money's gonna help us build
something that we've been one of the
biggest secrets of kamma that we've been
working
oh you can't go profitable you know I
love profitability guys you know I love
it you know I love making money I love
money
I love making money I love capitalism
build cool shit and people notice
there's no only people with money to
sell to a lot of people right well
hardware startup people think you can't
make money in hardware and like yeah if
you do Sarah you can't but doing a
Shenzhen hardware trip yeah yeah
anything are gonna go to China
well times go from China taking a
paycheck yet now no I still don't get
paid anything cop detection or that I'm
interested in I do love profitability
I love profit I love money I love making
money I love capitalism all right guys I
don't think these routes are gonna
process unfortunately so you know we're
gonna have to we're gonna have to wait
now we're gonna have to do this on
different periscope but that was the
first step and then there's the step of
waiting for Khamenei eye to finally
process your house which needs to get
better I'm not getting acquired by Tesla
when I get acquired by Tesla that's like
Android getting acquired by their play
recognition travel the concert
capitalism is good and shooty the
Cavanaugh's non-zero day the climate for
real you know I feel about that
capitalism for the rich socialism for
the poor no we do it the other way
around that it's terrible about just
capitalism for everybody there is no
current infrastructure guy there's no
current infrastructure guy take selfies
in China with dudes and soul I'm not
doing that man I love China I love going
to China and you know what I learned
from PewDiePie how to go to foreign
countries and be respectful no Google
doesn't get to away the Google's over
capitalism for the win that's right
no Google's over guys you know Google
nobody a quick google if you're a good
engineer come work here Google's not
building the future I do like kind of
food did I just need the files no I got
the files
got files need Cabana oh I say it's okay
no guys no so actually the route didn't
process it would have processed for you
it's just not gonna process for us
because we're running 0 for 4 and we
haven't updated the pipeline to process
0 for 4 rounds yet yeah no all routes go
to command accommoda I - he's insane
obstruction you guys are and it's just
shit for sure but we hired an
infrastructure to start Monday
that's all very exciting we also hired a
recruiter so I'm gonna show you the
recruiters desk get my Hep B um - guys
don't worry about that stuff hire from
New Zealand would you assist relocation
yeah we could do a relocation bonus sure
Tom Iowa this works on HTTPS doesn't it
hi guys this is this is the desk for the
recruiter um so we can have a recruiter
sitting right here and we got him this
beautiful piece of artwork you like this
artwork that's right I kind of like this
artwork no it's not guilfoyle
yeah yo yo it's exciting it's exciting
high schoo piece thanks for joining
sorry we couldn't periscope with you all
today we got Andy a new iMac problem and
that's why there could get the iMac who
was the recruiter yeah reach out give me
a job at comedy I much beep cool I know
I'd seen mr. robot peace